&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：你想知道为什么，谢谢你问我，我有三个
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: And you're wondering why and thanks for asking, I have three
为什么你总是喜欢这个东西，因为它会花费你更多的时间和
reasons why you should always prefer this thing that's gonna take you more time and
努力写出这些函数的所有名称，对吗？
effort to write out all those names to those functions, right?
我们知道计算机科学中经典的难题之一是命名
We know that one of the classic hard problems in computer science is naming
事情，而且，你告诉我必须去想出所有这些名字。
things, and, you're telling me I gotta go come up with all these names.
相信我，我也在同一条船上，每次我写函数，我都会说，我不知道
Trust me, I'm in the same boat, every time I write a function, I'm like, I don't know
怎么称呼这个东西，想不出一个好名字，我明白。
what to call this thing, can't come up with a good name, I understand that.
但有三个原因，我认为，一起，使一个坚实的理由，
But there are three reasons which I think, together, make a solid case,
这种努力是至关重要的，这是必要的，
that that effort is critical, that it's necessary,
您应该始终使用名称-函数表达式。
that you should always, always use name-function expressions.
因此，第一个首选名称函数表达式，因为名称产生或
So number one prefer a name function expression, because the name produces or
从函数内部创建对函数的可靠自引用。
creates a reliable self-reference to the function from inside of itself.
如果要使函数递归，这是很有用的。
That is useful if you're going to make the function recursive.
如果该函数是某种事件处理程序且
It's useful if that function is an event handler of some sort and
它需要引用自身来解除绑定。
it needs to reference itself to unbind itself.
如果您需要访问其上的任何属性，则此选项非常有用
It's useful if you need to access any properties on that
函数对象，例如它的链接或名称或其他类似的东西。
function object such as its link or its name or other thing of that sort.
任何时候您可能需要对函数的自我引用，
Anytime you might need a self reference to the function,
对这个问题唯一正确的答案是，它需要一个名字。
the single only right answer to that question is, it needs to have a name.
有一些ES6之前的黑客攻击或者甚至是ES5之前的黑客攻击，
There were some pre ES6 sorts of hacks or an even pre ES5 sorts of hacks,
您可以使用参数start call作为对函数的引用，
where you could use arguments start calling as a reference to the function,
它没有坏掉，但本质上已经过时了。
it's not broken but essentially deprecated.
从函数内部获取对函数的引用的方法
The way to get a reference to a function from inside of itself and
有一个可靠的参考就是使用你的函数表达式的名称。
have a reliable reference is to use the name of your function expression.
在前面示例中，当我有一个全局变量名时
In that previous example, when I had a variable name that was in the global
作用域，然后我有了我的函数表达式。
scope, and then I had my function expression.
它是更可靠还是更不可靠
Would it be more or less reliable for
让我引用我自己范围内只读的大理石，或者
me to make a reference to a marble in my own scope that is read only, or
引用非只读封闭范围中的大理石？
to reference a marble in an enclosing scope that is not read only?
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：如果我想从函数内部引用自己，并且
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: If I wanted to reference myself from inside of the function, and
我可以选择是用自己的大理石来指代自己
I had the choice between referencing myself with a marble in my own
范围为只读，我的函数表达式的名称。
scope that is read only, the name of my function expression.
或者我可以用函数中的变量自引用自己
Or I could self-reference myself with the variable that my function had
在外部作用域中分配给，默认情况下不是只读的。
be assigned to in the outer scope, which isn't by default read only.
这两个中的哪一个会是更好的自我引用？
Which one of those two would be the better self reference?
&gt；&gt；扬声器2：第一个。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: The first one.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：第一个，对，你拥有的那个
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: First one, right, the one that you own and
即只读是更可靠的自我引用。
that is read only is a more reliable self reference.
所以，第一，如果有任何可能远程你将
So, number one, if there's any possible chance remotely that you're gonna
需要一个自我引用，最好继续并命名它。
need a self reference, it's best to go ahead and name it.
即使你现在不需要它，你将来也可能需要它，
Even if you don't need it now, you might need it in the future,
最好是继续命名，这是第一个原因。
it's best to go ahead and name it, that's reason number one.
第二个原因，为什么你总是喜欢命名函数表达式。
Reason number two, why you should always prefer named function expressions.
你们中有多少人曾经遇到过JavaScript异常，必须通过以下方式进行调试
How many of you have ever had a JavaScript exception where you had to debug it by
在看堆栈跟踪吗？
looking at a stack trace?
好的，有多少人喜欢看匿名函数，一遍又一遍，
Okay, how many of you love seeing anonymous function, over and over again,
在你的堆栈痕迹中一行又一行？
line after line in your stack traces?
特别是当我们谈论被缩小的生产代码时，所以
Especially, when we're talking about production code that's been minified, so
他们都说第1行，字符32，712，
they all say line 1, character 32,712,
因为我们都知道那是哪个函数，对吧？
cuz we all know exactly which function that is, right?
猜猜如果为函数表达式使用名称会发生什么？
Guess what happens if you use a name for your function expressions?
它显示在堆栈跟踪中。
It shows up in the stack trace.
如果您使用一个好名称，而不是像Food Bar那样，而是像处理用户单击那样，
If you use a good name not like food bar, but like handle user click,
它将显示在堆栈跟踪中。
it's going to show up in the stack trace.
因此，通过自动命名您的函数，您可以使代码更易于调试，
So automatically by naming your functions, you make your code more debuggable,
您可以使堆栈跟踪更可调试。
you make your stack traces more debuggable.
事实上，我在很多场合看过堆栈跟踪，
Truth, I have on multiple occasions, looked at a stack trace that had good,
其中有用的语义名称，以及
useful semantic names in it, and
能够简单地通过查看名称和
been able to tell the source of the bug simply by looking at the names and
函数的顺序，什么没有被调用，什么被调用了。
the order of the functions, what didn't get called and what did get called.
甚至不需要看代码
Didn't even have to look at the code,
有了名字，我立刻就知道了漏洞是什么。
I knew immediately what the bug was just from having the names.
即使您必须查看代码，您仍然在接近代码
And even if you do have to look at the code, you're still approaching the code
从堆栈跟踪中获得比以前更多的心理环境。
with more mental context from that stack trace than you would before.
现在我认为规则在和
Now I think that rule in and
本身就足以证明总是为您的函数命名。
of itself is enough to justify always name your functions.
我不知道你，但我需要所有的帮助，我可以调试我的程序。
I don't know about you, but I need all the help I can debugging my programs.
所以，每次我必须调试时，额外的努力都会得到回报
So, the extra effort is gonna pay off in dividends every time I have to debug
密码。
the code.
第二，我们希望有可调试的堆栈跟踪。
Number two, we want to have debuggable stack traces.
第三，我个人认为这可能是最重要的，
And number three, and I think personally this might be the most important of all,
但它肯定是看起来最不明显的一个
but it's certainly the one that seems least obvious or
也许这对其他人来说更具争议性。
maybe it's a little more controversial to other people.
第三，通过在你的函数上加上一个名字，
Number three, by putting a name on your function,
您使代码更具自我文档化。
you make that code more self-documenting.
如果我有一个匿名函数，我查看该函数来找出
If I have a function that is anonymous, and I look at that function to figure out
匿名函数正在做什么，我必须读取函数体和
what that anonymous function is doing, I have to read the function body and
我可能还必须读取它被解析的位置。
I also probably have to read where it's being parsed.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：我必须从这两条信息中推断，
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: And I have to infer from those two pieces of information,
函数的目的。
the purpose of the function.
我也许能够推断出它处理用户点击的目的。
I may be able to infer the purposes that it handles user clicks.
但我宁愿读者不必推断它的目的是处理
But I would rather the reader not have to infer that its purpose is to handle
用户点击时，我可以把一个名称，使它完全和
user clicks when I could put a name there that makes it completely and
完全明确。
totally unambiguous.
名为handle user click的函数不需要任何其他
The function named handle user clicks doesn't require any other
读完剩下的代码，让我弄明白，
reading of the rest of the code, for me to figure out,
你想让我用这个功能处理用户点击，是吗？
you want me to handle user clicks with this function, yes?
&gt；&gt；演讲者3：所以这更像是一个最佳实践问题，看起来非常有说服力。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 3: So this is more of a best practices question seems very compelling.
我的第一反应是说，好吧，我就说出这个表达式的名字
My first instinct is then to say, okay, I'll just name the expression
我将命名上面作用域的变量，我假设，
the same thing that I will name the variable of the scope above, I'm assuming,
一，那是一起跟踪案件吗？
a, is that a case of shadowing?
和b，-&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：这是一个案例
And b,- &gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: It is a case of
跟踪。
shadowing.
&gt；&gt；扬声器3：在B，这可能是令人难以置信的碎片问题，或者是
&gt;&gt; Speaker 3: And at B, that's probably incredibly problematic for debris or is
这是会被考虑的事情-&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：我不会考虑
that something that would be considered- &gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: I wouldn't consider
影子是个问题还是不是个问题。
shadowing to be a problem or not a problem.
在这种情况下，我认为你不太可能需要
In that particular scenario, I think it is unlikely that you're gonna need to have
两个对函数的引用。
both references to the function.
也许你需要这样做，如果你这样做了，你就得给他们起个名字
Maybe you're gonna need to and if you do, you're gonna have to name them something
不同的是，你现在必须避免跟踪。
different, you're now gonna have to avoid shadowing.
但在大多数情况下，如果这个东西有一个明确的名字，
But in most cases, if there is one definitive name for what this thing is,
如果你想的话现在就说出他们的名字。
name both of them now if you want to.
我个人的观点是无论如何不要对变量做函数表达式，
My personal opinion is don't do function expression on the variable anyway,
做一个函数声明，只有一个名字，但是，如果你要
do a function declaration and there's just one name but, if you are going
为了制造一个变量，如果只有一个名字，可能会更有意义。
to make a variable then it probably makes more sense if there's only one name.
不过，这里有一些警告，因为有时，该函数的使用，
There are caveats to this, though, because sometimes, the usage of that function,
它被传递到哪里，或者它将要做什么，
where it's being passed to, or what it's going to do,
它可能有一个不同的目的，而不是你想要描述它的方式，无论是它本身还是它本身。
it may have a different purpose than how you wanna describe it, in and of itself.
所以实际上可能有一个不同的，更合适的名字
So it might in fact be that there's a different, more appropriate name for
函数，而不是分配给它的属性，或
the function, as opposed to what property it's being assigned to, or
它被赋值给了什么变量。
what variable it's being assigned to.
所以它们不一定是相同的，但有时它们可能是有用的？
So they are not necessarily the same, but sometimes they might be, helpful?
很好，所以我认为这三个加在一起，
Good, so these three I think, taken together,
做一个铁一般的例子，你的函数将
make an ironclad case that your functions would
如果您的函数是命名的，则编写更好的代码。
make better code if your functions are named.
现在我明白这对大多数人来说是有问题的
Now I understand that that is problematic for most people that have that
匿名编写函数的手指肌肉记忆。
finger muscle memory of writing the functions anonymously.
自从jQuery出现以来，我看到的每一个博客都在使用匿名函数。
That I've seen every single blog since the jQuery days, using anonymous functions.
你曾经有权访问匿名函数的每一段代码
That every piece of code you've ever had any access to anonymous functions
到处都是。
everywhere.
突然，有个人告诉你，不，
And all of a sudden, here's this one guy telling you, no, no, no,
那些都需要名字。
those all need names.
我明白，这是有问题的，很麻烦的，是额外的工作。
I get it, that's problematic, it's troublesome, it's extra work.
但是你必须回到我所说的关于代码的目的。
But you have to go back to what I said about the purpose of code.
编写代码的目的不是为了方便您键入。
The purpose of code is not to be convenient for you to type.
代码的目的是让您更清楚地传达您的意图。
The purpose of code is for you to communicate more clearly your intent.
这些问题都有解决的方法，但是
There are ways to solve each of these problems but
解决这些问题的最好方法是命名函数。
the best way to solve these problems is to name the function.
所以刚才有人问我，如果我给一个匿名函数赋值会发生什么
So someone asked just a moment ago, what happens if I assign an anonymous function
对于属性或变量之类的东西，名称会发生什么变化？
to property, or to a variable or something, what happens to the name?
嗯，它仍然是一个匿名函数，
Well, it's still an anonymous function,
它仍然没有对自己的词汇自我引用。
it still doesn't have a lexical self-reference to itself.
你能引用外部作用域中的变量吗？
Could you reference the variable in the outer scope?
当然可以，但它不太可靠，不太可信，而且
Of course you can, but it's a little less reliable, a little less trustable, and
我会争辩少一点语义。
I would argue a little less semantic.
它会在堆栈跟踪中显示名称吗？
Is it gonna show up with a name in the stack trace?
取决于该函数表达式存在的位置，
Depending upon where that function expression exists,
它也许可以推断出一个名字。
it might be able to have a name inferred.
例如，如果它被赋值给一个变量，
For example, if it's assigned to a variable,
然后通常只要没有一些复杂的解构代码在适当的地方，
then generally as long as there isn't some complex destructuring code in place,
一般情况下，它只会取名字并推断这就是你的意思
generally it's going to just take the name and infer that's what you mean for
堆栈跟踪的目的，除了这里有个大问题，99.9%
the purposes of the stack trace, except here is the big problem, 99.9%
在人们使用匿名函数的所有情况中，表达式是作为回调的。
of all cases where people use anonymous functions expressions is as callbacks.
它们直接以行方式将它们传递给其他函数，如.map，然后，
They pass them in line directly to other functions like .map, .then,
所有这些你猜怎么着？
all those and guess what?
当您在调用位置传递函数表达式时，
When you pass a function expression in a call position,
没有办法从它推断出任何名字。
there's no way to infer any name from it.
所以你得不到那个名字推断的好处，
So you don't get the benefit of that name inference,
您必须将其分配给变量以获得名称推断或分配给属性。
you have to assign it to a variable to get the name inference or to a property.
如果你想麻烦地把它赋值给一个变量，为什么
And if you're gonna go to the trouble to assign it to a variable why
而不仅仅是一份声明？
not just make it a declaration?
为什么要写一个变量，然后必须写两次名字？
Why write a variable and then have to write the name twice?
我看不出有什么理由你会强烈地喜欢做更多的工作
I don't see any reason why you should strongly prefer making more work for
让你自己变得更让人困惑。
yourself and making it a little bit more confusing for people.
这甚至不是唯一的区别，当我们稍后谈到提升时，我们是
And that's not even the only difference, when we talk about hoisting later we're
会看到吊装有很大的不同。
gonna see there's a big difference in hoisting.
所以我认为你应该更喜欢有名字的函数声明，如果你是
So I think you should prefer function declarations with names if you're
传入一个函数表达式，给它加上一个名字，就像如果它的话你会有的一样
gonna pass in a function expression, put a name on it just like you would have if it
是一个函数声明，则给它以相同的名称。
were a function declaration, give it the same name.
现在我明白了命名很难，但实际上是你唯一合法的理由
Now I understand that naming is hard but really the only legitimate reason why you
不要因为你太懒或没有创意而给你的函数命名。
don't name your functions cuz you're too lazy or uncreative to come up with a name.
没有理由认为匿名函数更可取。
There is no reason why an anonymous function is preferrable.
没有理由认为名字会分散注意力或
There is no argument that can be made that that name is distracting or
对代码可读性没有帮助。
is unhelpful for the purposes of code readability.
人们提出的任何论点到那种程度都是胡说八道。
Any argument that people have made to that extent is complete bunk.
人们在书和博客里到处告诉你，不，
People tell you all over the place in books and blogs, no, no,
不，所有那些额外的东西都是完全不必要的。
no, all that extra stuff is totally unnecessary.
他们对此的想法是完全错误的，
And they're thinking completely wrongly about this,
因为他们没有考虑好的语义名称的目的。
cuz they're not thinking about the purpose of good semantic names.
函数名的目的是告诉你为什么这个东西存在。
The purpose of a function name is to tell you why does this thing exist.
我的断言是，程序中存在的每个函数，
My assertion is that every function that exists in your program,
每一个功能都有一个目的。
every single function has a purpose.
如果每个函数都有用途，这意味着每个函数都有名称。
And if every function has a purpose, it means every function has a name.
这取决于您想出这个名称并将其放入您的代码中，而不是Make
And it's up to you to come up with that name and put it in your code, not make
代码的阅读器必须在每次读取代码时都弄明白。
the reader of your code have to figure it out every single time they read the code.
如果你找不出函数的名字，
If you can not come up with a name for the function,
这可能意味着你还不理解这个函数。
it probably means that you don't understand that function yet.
这可能意味着，这个函数太复杂了，
It probably means, that function is too complex,
并且需要被分解成更小的碎片，直到这样的时候
and needs to be broken down into smaller pieces until such a time
因为这些名字完全是显而易见的，然后把它们放在那里。
as those names are completely self obvious, and then put them there.
它是更有问题的代码的先行指示器，当您不能
It's a leading indicator of more problematic code when you can't
想出一个名字或者
come up with a name or
你能想出的名字有14个字长，就像我们在Java中做的那样，好吗？
the name that you can come up with is 14 words long like we do in Java, okay?
这通常意味着这个函数做的太多了。
That usually means this function is doing too much.
这里有个问题，是吗？
There was a question over here, yes?
&gt；&gt；扬声器4：那么你是说匿名函数的使用
&gt;&gt; Speaker 4: So are you saying that the use of anonymous functions
就是少打字，真的就是这样。
is really just to type less, that's really all.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：这正是我想说的，而且
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: That's exactly what I'm saying, and
当我们转到下一张幻灯片时，情况会变得更糟，是的。
it gets worse when we go to the next slide, yes.
&gt；&gt；演讲者5：所以听起来你肯定更喜欢声明，
&gt;&gt; Speaker 5: So it sounds like you definitely prefer declarations,
函数表达式有没有很好的用途？
is there ever, is there a good use for a function expression?
&GT；&GT；Kyle Simpson：是的，当然，
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Yeah, absolutely,
函数表达式有时是绝对必要的。
function expression sometimes are absolutely necessary.
我个人的经验，除了你必须去的地方，
My personal rule of thumb, other than places where you have to,
我个人的经验是，如果函数声明超过
my personal rule of thumb is that I prefer function declaration if it's more than
三行代码。
three lines of code.
如果只有一行、两行或三行代码，
If it's one, two, or three lines of code,
通常我会让它成为一个内联函数表达式。
generally I'm gonna make that an inline function expression.
除非，那个东西需要被多次调用，在这种情况下，
Unless, that thing needs to be called multiple times, in which case,
我将使它成为一个函数声明，即使它只有一行。
I'm gonna make it a function declaration, even if it's one line.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：但这些只是一般的指导方针，以防万一，
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: But those are just sort of general guidelines in case,
你的里程可能会有所不同，就像他们说的，好吗？
your mileage may vary, as they say, okay?
所以你猜怎么着，我仍然在挣扎，尽管
So guess what, I still struggle with this, even though for
多年来，我一直在宣扬这个信息，并告诉人们。
years I've been preaching this message and telling people.
你是第万个听我这么说的学生，对吧？
And you're the 10,000th student to ever hear me say this, right?
我已经在全世界说了这么多年了
I've said this all over the world for years and
我仍然在这个问题上挣扎，这里是我使用的技巧。
I still struggle with this problem and here's the trick that I use.
第一，我从来不会只写一次代码然后就结束了，
Number one, I don't ever write code just once and then I'm done with it,
在我重构代码的过程中，代码总是一个迭代的过程。
code is always an iterative process where I'm refactoring it.
当我开始编写函数时，我几乎肯定还不知道具体是如何和
When I start to write a function, I almost certainly don't know yet exactly how and
这个函数是用来做什么的或者这个结构是用来做什么的。
what that function's gonna be for or what the structure's gonna be.
所以我只能接受这样一个事实，无论我想出的名字都不是用来写的
So I just accept the fact that whatever name I come up with is not written in
斯通和我要换好几次。
stone and I'm gonna change it multiple times.
如果我还不能合法地想出任何好名字，
And if I legitimately can't come up with any good name yet,
我从名字TODO开始，T-O-D-O，因为我有搜索的习惯
I start with the name TODO, T-O-D-O because I'm in a habit of searching for
在我提交东西之前要做的评论。
TODO comments before I commit things.
我会找到那些未命名的函数
And I'll find those unnamed functions and
在这一点上，也许对它应该叫什么有更好的感觉。
at that point maybe have a better sense of what it ought to be called.
仍然是一个你必须工作的过程，它仍然是一个努力，它仍然是我的
Still a process that you have to work on, it is still an effort, and it still my
灭绝的习惯，即使这么多年后，我从匿名开始
extinctual habit even all these years later that I start with the anonymous
函数，但后来我意识到所有这些好处，我回去给它们命名。
function but then I realized all of these benefits and I go back and I name them.